After we have massaged both legs with a hot stone, I'm going to show you how I place the stones on the legs.
We're using a larger placement stones.
Two stones over the Hamstrings .
If it feel too warm you can double up on the sheet.
But always check in with your client and how the temperature is.
Then we're going to place around the sheet stone on the Calf.
And I like to cover the stones with sheet to keep them in place and also to keep the heat in.
I'm going to do this on both sides of the legs.
Larger stones on the larger muscle groups.
Covering them to keep them in place and to retain the heat.
Another larger stone round in shape to cover the Calf.
I like to do some compressions just to soothe the heat into the muscles.
And for an extra treat I like the client to hold a stone in each hand.
Interactive.
If they have cold hands, it's great for warming.
And that's tone placement on the legs in prone.